I'll take my hand and pull out the light.
I'll take my hand and turn on the light.
I'm the one who's for you.
I'm drawing my hand and paint my face.
I really should get to those samurai
before someone else steals all the glory.
It's time to get serious.
A little hands-on time and
he'll melt in an instant.
Ready to broadcast his message all over
the island, Cayman lady? Yes, ma 'am.
All right, black leg.
I'm very busy, so time for
you to call Nico Robin.
You don't want to keep my girls
waiting all night, do you?
We've set up a very
elaborate trap, you see.
My webs, hard gum I call them,
are lining the entrance in layers.
They're lining the floor, too.
So one step inside and you're stuck.
My subordinates are waiting with
tranquilizer guns to fire on my prey.
The rest is up to you.
So call Nico Robin or I'll make you pay!
Come on!
I'm in a hurry here!
I need to go finish off those samurai!
Robin.
What I want is to join you. What?
I...
I want to live!
Stubborn, aren't you?
Come!
Come on! Come on!
Oh, Sam!
I can hardly watch me!
What a pretty man!
He'd do anything to save his courage!
Now he'll die without saying a word!
He's still in my heart! But
he'll ask! He's our fault!
Wait! No!
You want me to talk?
All right, then.
I've got a few words.
He's going to say something like,
Blackleg, don't do it!
He'll really make you suffer.
Robin, I'm sorry.
It looks like this is it for me.
I wish I could have seen
you smile one last time.
Help me Robin!
Help me please!
He called her for help after all that!
I'm on the third floor
in the banquet hall!
No!
I've been taken hostage!
I'm sorry! Sanji.
They said if you don't come
here soon, they'll kill me!
My life is in your hands!
Please, come rescue me!
Pathetic.
Put the bastard out of his misery.
One of the star hats is in trouble!
Oh, no!
A broadcast?
They must want all of
Onigashima to hear it.
Nico Robin is one of the most
important figures in the world.
Of course, it figures that
they're after her knowledge.
Sounds like they're trying
to lead Robin into a trap.
It's one thing for a man to cry
if that's downright whining.
Those Straw Hats are one of a kind.
I bet a woman got him
and he won't fight back.
Go figure.
Hey, Nami! Sanji's voice!
It's coming from that cat!
Be careful!
I saw one earlier.
They all have that
weird eye on their face.
I'm begging you!
Robin!
I can't believe it.
Alright, I called for Robin.
Keep your word. Untie me.
Someone's here, and it sounds
like we're under attack.
Well, that was fast.
You're so naive.
You think I'd let you go?
If I recall, you said you loved me, right?
That means this matter
isn't business anymore.
It's personal.
You can be my precious pet.
You'll fit in with the
rest of them perfectly.
I'll make your body
unable to live without me.
We love you and you
alone, Lady Black Maria.
Impossible.
Because I want to love all the ladies!
Being unfaithful already?
Then you'll have to be PUNISHED! Hold on!
I don't want to hurt a lady's fist!
I'll drop my armament, Haki!
Mille Fleurs, go!
Gigantatamano!
And space!
My lady!
How did you manage to get in here?
My flowers can bloom anywhere.
You dare to slap my face!
That wasn't much of a plan.
You thought I'd walk straight into
your trap just because Sanji called me?
I'm so glad you're here!
I was part of an evil
organization for quite a while.
So I can't help but show
my devilish side sometimes.
Especially if someone is foolish
enough to harm my friends.
I beg your pardon, just passing through
with the cold gales of the underworld.
Bad news, our entire ambush
unit has been taken out.
The traps were destroyed too.
He froze the threads and shattered them.
I'm a bit surprised it
turned out quite so well.
Well, the wicked winds of
hell know no bounds. Yuh-ho?
You're scarier!
Oh, you're one to talk!
Thanks, Rook.
I think you might have saved my life.
Anytime and anyplace.
I hate to say it.
I'd be better off helping Kin'emon
and the others on the roof.
For some reason, I feel like
I just can't win this one.
You're right about that.
Come back, Blackleg!
You were meant to be my pet!
I won't let you go!
Any last words?
Or is that it?
Why are you protecting that
idiot when he sold you out?
You really think he's worth your life?
How sad.
You don't have friends.
If you did, you would
surely understand. Huh?
It's a fine thing, trusting someone.
Sanji!
Thanks for counting on me.
I mean it.
That made me happy.
Oh, wait!
Watch the eyes!
Yeah.
Good luck, you two!
Mice don't normally do that.
It's from Father's surveillance team.
They're known as the Marys.
It's a cyborg, thus the smoke.
They're modified animals.
They've been fitted with
mechanical body parts.
How strange!
These creatures wander around the
island without a particular objective.
But they can share what they see.
And the human Marys take note.
But where else could we go?
Sure this is where they're at?
Hard to say since no one's been
to this cursed place in ages.
Doesn't look like
anyone's opened the door.
Broken in even.
Hey, we got nothing else to go on.
Let's bust in there and find out!
Kill the kid, and young Master
Yamato can be the next Shogun!
It sounds like they sent a whole team.
And if we stay here long,
they're only going to send more.
Let's run, Yamato.
Can you help us find a path that will
keep Lord Momonosuke out of their sights?
We know you're in there!
Come on out!
Two Monkeys break down the door!
One, two!
We have to move, now!
I'm sorry, Momonosuke.
I need you to hide in my clothes.
What?
Time to go, Shinobu!
I thought the idea was to
stay hidden from the enemy!
Not to worry!
We'll keep Momonosuke hidden
till we knock them out!
That is not what I meant at all! Die!
Uh, no need to worry, Master Jack.
We're blocking this passage for you.
You really should get some rest.
Shut up!
Out of my way!
How long are the Akazaya Samurai
still in the treasure repository?
They sure are!
Black Maria, where are you?
I'm still in the banquet hall.
All right, stay there and I'll
finish off the samurai myself.
Even if they're badly
injured, they're strong.
Too strong to fall to one
of the Toby rope bone.
This is my battle. Understand?
Really underestimating
me, aren't you, Jack?
But that's fine.
It works out this time.
The prey here is far more interesting.
What is that thing? A weapon?
It won't be long now, Nico Robin.
Soon you'll belong to Kaido.
I'll make sure of that.
Not likely.
You'd have to kill me first.
She's so cool!
A SPLENDID EFFORT,
WARRIORS OF THE FULL MOON!
I pity your power is lickety
limited by the whims of the weather.
Hydro!
Listen, you Karoo must
keep moving forward!
I can't die.
I won't stop till I avenge Pedro.
What are you avenging, girl?
This is war.
Pedro was prepared to die.
Why did you come to Big Mom's
territory in the first place?
Because it sure as hell
wasn't for a lickety picnic.
If you want to live that
bad, you should stay home.
Go frolicking in the damn forest.
Your days of playing
Pirate are over, Bunny.
Alright, I'm not fond of this lickety
alliance with the Beast Pirates, but oh well.
If that's what Mama
decided, I have no choice.
Besides, it's a good chance to teach those
worst generation punks a lickety lesson.
And they're running!
The enemy leader
Momonosuke is getting away!
If nobody stops him,
there's gonna be trouble!
He must be hiding Momonosuke somehow!
I haven't been able to spot him yet.
The Momonosuke is there with young
Master Yamato and the Kunoichi.
I know it!
It's cramped and difficult to
breathe in here, but never mind that.
For some reason, even though my life is
in danger, I feel like I'm in heaven.
Quick, Shinobu, this way.
Of course, if they keep coming!
Can you take us somewhere else, please?
We need to get out of sight!
It's under control.
They can't see us once
they're unconscious, you know?
If we could find a place to hide, then
they would never see us in the first place!
Did you get that, everybody?
Momonosuke has a speech from
the Forbidden Storehouse.
He's with young Master
Yamato at the Konorichi.
Without a doubt.
Another broadcast, huh?
Now they're going after Momo and Shinobu.
But who is Yamato?
Well, whatever.
Hey, where's the Forbidden Storehouse?
I'll never tell you.
Yeah?
Ugh!
The front of the skull dome!
It's right near the front entrance!
Kinemon's group should be at
the back of the castle tower.
What a pain.
That's the opposite way.
Kin'emon and the others are
injured from fighting Kaido.
Momo and Shinobu are
being chased by gifters.
I don't know who needs me more!
How do I decide?
No time to think about it.
Let's see.
Whoever needs me the most
has got to be this way.
I can't.
This blue flame draws out my strength.
But it's all spent.
There's nothing left.
Keep fighting, dig deeper
than you ever have before.
If you don't, the next time
you turn into an ice soda?
You'll run wild till you die!
This is no time to despair, young man.
Stand up and show some courage.
Mr.
Raccoon is enduring the same pain as you,
but he's still working on those antidotes.
We can't give up before he does.
Boss?
What happened to you?
I've still got some fight
left, even if I'm old.
A true samurai fights to the end!
Stand back!
I'll show you how it's done!
Help, Apoo! Please!
We can't win without you!
The antibody's right there,
but we can't break through their
defense no matter what we try!
We're all going to die
at this rate, but why?
We're on Master Queen's side!
No point in whining about it.
He doesn't give a damn!
Damn, we're so close,
all we gotta do is kill one measly
raccoon and the antibody is ours!
Damn it, Drake!
This is all your fault,
you stinkin' traitor!
Stop pretending you're some kind of hero!
Drake isn't the only problem
we're dealing with right now.
The withered old man
got his strength back!
Don't ask me how he pulled that one off.
Everyone in Wano either
respected or feared this man.
Hyogoro the flower.
That's an iron-tight defense
if I've ever seen one.
We're not getting anywhere near that
raccoon with both of them guarding him.
What happened to Hyogoro?
He was just a little old man a second ago!
That's what he looked
like back in his prime,
when Kaido was pounding down
his door trying to recruit him.
Yeah, I can't stop shaking.
Are you alright, boss?
It's still you in there?
Yes.
I can feel the chill, but that's fine.
My mind is sharp, and my body is ready.
The virus got me, but not how I expected.
It's drunk out all my strength,
down to the last inch of my life.
If that's what it's come to, fine!
I can put this final burst
of power to good use.
In exchange for this life that I give,
I'll cut down all of
their strongest fighters.
Now come at me if you dare!
Friends, listen closely. Yes!
We're ready, boss!
Win or lose, I don't think
I have much time left.
There's a chance Mr.
Raccoon's Cure won't
make it to me in time.
In other words, I might
turn into a nice Oni.
We can't have that.
If it happens, cut me
down without hesitation.
That's the only way.
Otherwise, I'll go after you all.
attacking like a wild animal and I
won't stop until you're dead at my feet.
I could never; we must,
and we must do it the instant he
begins to lose himself to the plague.
If he becomes an oni,
he'll be unstoppable.
I'm counting on you!
Don't worry—we'll handle
him; we have a reputation.
reputation We were the
Mimawari Kuma, after all.
As for your tales of glory, we'll
consign them to the pages of history.
Move it or die!
Here we come!
One sword style of the flower.
Special technique.
Slamming hair!
Of Holy Rage!
Goal!
Everyone attack at once! Let's go!
It's funny, Odin.
I always think of what could have been.
I can't help but wonder if
we might have beaten Kaido.
If we'd challenged him
back when I was young.
But there's no need for regrets.
Kin'emon and the others have
executed a perfect raid.
And I met a fascinating man.
One who became my disciple, in a sense.
Listen, Mr.
Straw Hat, you have much
more potential to unlock.
I'm certain that you'll see it in time.
Remember, in the midst of danger
is when true power blossoms.
If we team up, we can win this.
Of course you can.
I can punch through anything
now that you've taught me Ryu.
This time I'll kick Kaido's sorry ass.
Those were words of unshakable
conviction and I still believe them.
He'll achieve mastery of
Ryu and become stronger.
Kaido will fall.
Your dream yet lives, Odin.
The land of water will be reborn.
A new dawn will come at last.
Oh hell, no!
He's gonna wipe out the whole floor!
Suck on this, you old fart!
He's not your only enemy here.
Watch your back.
Marco!
The hell did you do to me?
Was that a shockwave? I don't know.
Keep fighting me and
maybe you'll find out.
You won't lay a finger on
those samurai on my watch.
If you want my head,
you'd better get to jump.
You wanna jump in the frying pan? Fire!
Help yourself!
Go to hell, you stupid
chicken! Ah, nothing!
Ha!
Bluebird!
you bastard you've had
enough fun i'm putting
you down i'll use your
feathers to pick my teeth
This ain't easy.
Both these guys have
bounties worth over a billy.
There's a limit to how long
I can keep holding them off.
You're gonna pay him!
You better hurry, Raccoon.
What lickety-damn?
I do believe that's Marco over there.
Lickety looks like he's seen better days.
Lick.
They're turning back into
Oni one after another.
It's gone!
The fire went away!
Do it.
I'm not afraid.
This is a blessing.
A parting gift you might say.
I thought that all I had left to do was
wait for death, and yet I came this far.
Well, this is enough.
I won't put your lives at
risk because I was careless.
I'm sorry to give you such a grisly
task, but please do this for me.
I leave Wano's future in your hands,
so ends Yoguro the flower.
I have no regrets.
I am at peace.